lindtusa.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Lindt Chocolate

Last Modified: November 2, 2014

This is the official privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") of Lindt & Sprüngli (USA) Inc. ("Lindt"), makers of fine chocolates. We at Lindt respect your concerns about privacy. Accordingly, we have adopted the following Privacy Policy which describes the information we collect about you from this, and other websites operated by Lindt & Sprüngli (USA) Inc. (the "website"), as well as why and how we use it. We also explain the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. By using this website, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via our website (collectively, the "website"), you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, our Privacy Policy will periodically change and evolve. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.

Information Collected

Personal Information

We will not collect any personal information about you (such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, age/year of birth (hereafter, "Personal Information") through our website unless you provide it to us voluntarily. You are not required to register or otherwise "sign in" to browse and enjoy our site.

We collect Personal Information from you when you voluntarily request our services, such as when you establish or update an account, enter a contest, sweepstakes or promotion, participate in a survey, quiz or poll, shop online, check the status of an order or review your order history, join our mailing list or our social networking sites, purchase and send gift cards, or subscribe to our newsletters.

Non-Personal Information

We may also gather "non-personal" information from our visitors. Such "non-personal information" may include user demographics or navigational information such as the length of time a visitor spends on our website, the pages that were visited, the length of time spent on each page, and the links that are clicked. Non-personal information may also include technical information such as your IP address. We reserve the right to use or disclose non-personal information but only subject to the terms and limitations set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may also collect information from third-party sources, including from social media and other websites that may display authorized Lindt branding. When you send us a message on Twitter, post a comment on our Facebook page, or on our interactive blog, we may collect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Submissions that you make to public areas of the website, such as (but not limited to) comments on our interactive blog, will be deemed public, and will not be deemed Personal Information. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the actions of other users of our website with respect to any information you choose to post in any public areas. We encourage you to refrain from providing or sharing personal information about yourself in blog comment threads, and other areas where your submissions may be available to the public. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy.

Use of Information We Collect

We use the Personal Information we collect from you primarily to provide to you a service that you have voluntarily requested. If you choose to make a purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. When you enter a sweepstakes or contest online, we may collect your name, mailing address, email address, age/year of birth and telephone number. This information is used for prize qualification, fulfillment and verification of eligibility. When you submit a question to our customer service, we use your email address or telephone number to respond to your inquiry.

We may also use the Personal Information that we collect to send you notifications, updates, catalogs, and advertisements (hereafter "Communications") via email or regular mail of special offers, services, products and promotions that may be of interest to you. Like all services provided through our website, the choice to receive our Communications is optional and you may change your preference at any time by choosing to unsubscribe or opt-out of receiving them.

We use aggregated non-personal information about our visitors to understand our website's demographics, such as the number of visitors accessing a certain location and the geographic distribution of our visitors. This information allows us to see what areas are most visited and enables us to improve the overall quality of our visitors' online experience by delivering more of the preferred areas and features that our visitors enjoy. We may also use the personal or non-personal information that we collect to analyze how our site is being used, and for marketing and promotional efforts, including direct marketing so that we can display and/or send you information about products or services that may be of interest to you.

Information Sharing with Third-Parties

Service Providers and Advertisers

To respect our visitors' privacy, we will not sell or rent the Personal Information you provide to us online to any third party. We may share the aggregate non-personal information that we collect with third parties, including service providers and advertisers. This aggregate information does not include your Personal Information.

We sometimes engage unaffiliated businesses to assist us in providing certain services. We may use third parties to provide marketing and promotional assistance, such as in connection with sweepstakes, contests, promotions or surveys (collectively, "Promotions"), to provide e-mail services, deliver advertisements, or facilitate sales and our online services, such as payment processors. We authorize these third parties to use your Personal Information solely in connection with the specific service that we have authorized the third party to provide on our behalf. We do not authorize them to use your Personal Information for any other reason. Our third-party service providers are bound by confidentiality obligations.

When we conduct Promotions, or contract with unaffiliated companies to do so, visitors or customers who choose to participate may be asked to provide Personal Information. Lindt and the other participating companies may use this information for such purposes as notifying and verifying prize winners and fulfilling certain promotional obligations. Information from these activities may also be used to explore future promotional opportunities or fulfill contractual obligations. At the point of registration, you may be given the option of opting-in to receive Communications. You may choose not to participate in Promotions if you do not wish to receive Communications from us or share your information with us and the other companies sponsoring Promotions. Even if you have chosen not to receive Communications from us prior to your participation in a Promotion, you may still receive information from us in connection with such activity if you register for or participate in the Promotion, but you may subsequently opt-out of receiving such Communications.

We may also allow reputable third parties, including advertisers, to collect information about your online activities through cookies and other technologies so that these third parties can provide services to us. These selected companies may use information about your activities on our site to provide advertisements about our products and services on this and other websites that you may visit. To prevent third parties from collecting and using this information, we would encourage you to disable all third-party cookies in your browser.

Disclosures Required By Law

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with law, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Lindt, our associates, employees or our clients. This may include assistance in fraud protection, investigation, credit or debt collection.

Lindt's Business Transactions

As we continue to grow and expand, we may engage in certain business transactions such as the assignment, purchase, sale, or merging of our company with other businesses. Personal Information and non-personal information that we and other participating businesses have collected would likely be transferred in such a commercial transaction. In connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of our business, we will attempt to ensure that any such buyer or assignee agrees to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Children

Our website is not designed for use by children under the age of thirteen. We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen, and we do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under thirteen, we will take immediate steps to delete the information.

Access to Personal Information

Our goal is to provide our customers with the best service possible. To do this, we need to make sure that our information is accurate, current, and reliable for its intended use. In order to provide you with the best service possible, we actively attempt to ensure that all contact information is accurate and up-to-date. If your personal information changes or if you no longer wish to receive our Communications, you may correct, amend, or delete your information at any time. If you are a registered user of the website, you can access, correct, update or remove your information in our databases any time by logging into My Account, by contacting our [Customer Service Department](http://www.lindtusa.com/shop/LindtContactUsView), or by calling 1-877-MY-LINDT (1-877-695-4638).

Cookies and Other Technologies

We use cookies to give our visitors a more personalized shopping experience and to help our visitors navigate our site more efficiently. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about the user. Cookies can make your web experience more enjoyable by storing passwords, preferences, and personalizing pages. Cookies can also help you be more efficient. For example, cookies allow you to add merchandise to your shopping cart and proceed to our online Checkout area. If you elect to leave our site without making a purchase, cookies can enable the item(s) you added to your shopping cart to remain there until you return to make a purchase or otherwise visit our website. You can adjust your browser settings to refuse all cookies or to inform you when a cookie is being placed on your hard drive.

We may use tracking pixels (also known as "pixel tags" and "web beacons"), or other similar technologies to measure and improve the effectiveness of our online services.

We allow some of our business partners to place their logo and a link on our web site if we think their business may be of interest to you. Please be aware that even though we try to choose partners who adhere to similar privacy standards and practices, we cannot control their use of cookies in relation to these links, nor can we control their use of Personal Information that you may submit to these third parties. We are not responsible for the data tracking, privacy practices or the content of such other websites. If you provide any Personal Information through any such third party website, such information will be controlled by the privacy policy of that third party. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of all the sites you visit through links from our website.

Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. Whether you purchase a product, send a gift, or request our Communications, you do so under encryption/security policies and technological safeguards that are consistent with industry standards. Please remember, however, that some risk always exists in transmitting information electronically over the Internet, and we cannot guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted prior to our collection.

We restrict access to Personal Information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information to perform a specific job, and to operate, improve, and fulfill our services. Questions regarding our Privacy Policy can be answered at any time by contacting [Customer Service](http://www.lindtusa.com/shop/LindtContactUsView) or by calling 1-877-MY-LINDT (1-877-695-4638).

Privacy Policy Updates

Lindt may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes, we will post them here. If we make material changes, we will place a notice on our website or we may send a notice to the email address you provided to us. You may wish to periodically refer back to our Privacy Policy to ensure that you are aware of our current policy.

Effective as of November 2, 2014
